my737ng.com 2017-12-15

# PRIVACY • my737NG

my737NG.com understands that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”).

**“Personally Identifiable Information”** refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name and email address. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?** We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?  **We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site offerings. We may email Visitors about research pertaining to the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.

**With whom may the information may be shared?** Personally Identifiable Information about our Visitors is not shared with any third party.

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?  **Personally Identifiable Information collected by my737NG.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties to my737NG.com.

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?  **Visitors  may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at [info@my737NG.com](mailto:info@my737ng.com).

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?  **Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the login state and preferences of our Visitors.

**How does my737NG.com use login information?** my737NG.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law.** We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors.

**How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?** Site software is kept up to date to maintain security. Our hosting provider protects the security of the server. We do not collect sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers. While we take reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors for any such occurrences.

**How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?  **Visitors may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at [info@my737NG.com](mailto:info@my737ng.com).

**Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?  **We provide Visitors with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site’s database by accessing their user account. However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor’s entry without retaining some residual information.

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?  **We will let our Visitors know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor to allow such Visitor to prevent such disclosure.

**Links:  **This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
